<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Evaporated: Gone with the Gods</title><link>https://open.spotify.com/show/6haxSH3TMIrt4BSFicMUgK</link><description>What if someone close to you just … vanished one day? That happens to tens of thousands of families a year in Japan, and it happened to Jake  Adelstein, too, back in 2018 — when his accountant disappeared, just before tax day. Adelstein, the author of Tokyo Vice, and co-host Shoko  Plambeck go in search of that missing accountant, and take us on a  journey into the fascinating and bizarre world of Japan’s johatsu, or “evaporated” people.  The Evaporated: Gone With the Gods is part of The Binge - subscribe to listen to all episodes, all at once, ad-free right now.     From serial killer nurses to psychic scammers – The Binge is your home for true crime stories that pull you in and never let go.      Follow The Binge Crimes and The Binge Cases wherever you get your podcasts to get new stories on the first of the month, every month.   Hit ‘Subscribe’ at the top of the The Evaporated: Gone With the Gods show page on Apple Podcasts or visit GetTheBinge.com. The Binge – feed your true crime obsession.   A Sony Music Entertainment and Campside Media production.   Find out more about The Binge and other podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts and follow us @sonypodcasts. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>https://i.scdn.co/image/ab6765630000ba8a6210a8c540973cb0c18adf70</url><title>Evaporated: Gone with the Gods</title><link>https://open.spotify.com/show/6haxSH3TMIrt4BSFicMUgK</link></image><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 06:16:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Episode 9: The Right to Disappear</title><link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/71W8CJ7e984tCRHBGnIzmB</link><description>One mystery is solved – Morimoto is alive. But finding him raises a question: Do those who disappear to start a new life have the right to stay missing?      Subscribe to The Binge to get all episodes of The Evaporated: Gone with the Gods, ad-free right now. Click ‘try free’ at the top of the Evaporated: Gone with the Godsshow page on Apple Podcasts to start your free trial or visit GetTheBinge.com to get access wherever you  get  your  podcasts.    A Campside Media &amp; Sony Music Entertainment production. Find more      great podcasts from SonyMusic Entertainment at   sonymusic.com/podcasts Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Episode 8: Conspiracy on the Coast</title><link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5eI53H6aiCWRjGdfYG8zRM</link><description>A series of evaporations on the western coastline of Japan eluded families and investigators for nearly 25 years. One theory – international espionage.      Subscribe to The Binge to get all episodes of The Evaporated: Gone     with the Gods, ad-free right now. Click ‘try free’ at the top of the     Evaporated: Gone with the Godsshow page on Apple Podcasts to start   your   free trial or visit GetTheBinge.com to get access wherever you   get  your  podcasts.    A Campside Media &amp; Sony Music Entertainment production. Find more     great podcasts from SonyMusic Entertainment at  sonymusic.com/podcasts     Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Episode 7: The March Room</title><link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6mcbhclrUHYy7A0fwnInNq</link><description>Tiphaine Veron, a French tourist, went missing in 2018. Understanding the circumstances around her disappearance –and the lasting ripple effect of the investigation–leads Jake and Shoko to Nikko.      Subscribe to The Binge to get all episodes of The Evaporated: Gone    with the Gods, ad-free right now. Click ‘try free’ at the top of the    Evaporated: Gone with the Godsshow page on Apple Podcasts to start  your   free trial or visit GetTheBinge.com to get access wherever you  get  your  podcasts.    A Campside Media &amp; Sony Music Entertainment production. Find more    great podcasts from SonyMusic Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Episode 6: Sakura Sachiko Does Not Exist</title><link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/47wXIhDgb8ivLOVmhlEb1y</link><description>Jake and Shoko leave Tokyo to go to a big-shot detective school in Sapporo. They learn how to solve missing persons cases — from some of the best detectives in Japan.    Subscribe to The Binge to get all episodes of The Evaporated: Gone   with the Gods, ad-free right now. Click ‘try free’ at the top of the   Evaporated: Gone with the Godsshow page on Apple Podcasts to start your   free trial or visit GetTheBinge.com to get access wherever you get  your  podcasts.    A Campside Media &amp; Sony Music Entertainment production. Find more   great podcasts from SonyMusic Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts     Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Episode 5: Vanishing By The Book</title><link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/45F0sA3VVdgTLs8PGMTs1o</link><description>Japan has some very strange –and dark– instructional manuals. Some of them can help you vanish…or commit the perfect crime.      Subscribe to The Binge to get all episodes of The Evaporated: Gone  with the Gods, ad-free right now. Click ‘try free’ at the top of the  Evaporated: Gone with the Godsshow page on Apple Podcasts to start your  free trial or visit GetTheBinge.com to get access wherever you get your  podcasts.    A Campside Media &amp; Sony Music Entertainment production. Find more  great podcasts from SonyMusic Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Episode 4: Pay or Sink</title><link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/5CtHkz1Jj4ZmqGvbH4td6l</link><description>Morimoto’s former boss tried to do him a favor, and got into a whole lot of trouble instead. We're talking about angry yakuza clients and charges to his credit card from sugar daddy websites. No sign of Morimoto since.    Subscribe to The Binge to get all episodes of The Evaporated: Gone with the Gods, ad-free right now. Click ‘try free’ at the top of the Evaporated: Gone with the Godsshow page on Apple Podcasts to start your free trial or visit GetTheBinge.com to get access wherever you get your podcasts.    A Campside Media &amp; Sony Music Entertainment production. Find more great podcasts from SonyMusic Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Episode 3: Sugimoto! You Bastard!</title><link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/6qnqlbAXqL1PqBRazNacPl</link><description>Sugimoto-san is a driver for Saita-san’s yonige company. But he’s also a former client. Who built a huge golf course … and got in way over his head.    Subscribe to The Binge to get all episodes of The Evaporated: Gone with the Gods, ad-free right now. Click ‘try free’ at the top of the Evaporated: Gone with the Godsshow page on Apple Podcasts to start your free trial or visit GetTheBinge.com to get access wherever you get your podcasts.    A Campside Media &amp; Sony Music Entertainment production. Find more great podcasts from SonyMusic Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Episode 2: Queen of the Night Movers</title><link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3pPI3rMPLZuBPiT8G9Sacy</link><description>Jake and Shoko aren’t meeting the CEO of your average moving company.  This is Miho Saita, the owner of a yonige–or, night moving–company. Night fleeing, to be precise.    Subscribe to The Binge to get all episodes of The Evaporated: Gone with the Gods, ad-free right now. Click ‘try free’ at the top of the Evaporated: Gone with the Godsshow page on Apple Podcasts to start your free trial or visit GetTheBinge.com to get access wherever you get your podcasts.    A Campside Media &amp; Sony Music Entertainment production. Find more great podcasts from SonyMusic Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Episode 1: The Missing Accountant</title><link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/67yAnHr5ygHKWjMwjl309q</link><description>Morimoto is Jake’s trusted accountant and friend.  So when Steve and Becky need an accountant, Jake is more than happy to recommend Morimoto. But as time goes on, Steve and Becky start to realize their new accountant might be hiding something. Just when the truth starts to show itself, Morimoto…evaporates.    Subscribe to The Binge to get all episodes of The Evaporated: Gone with the Gods, ad-free right now. Click ‘try free’ at the top of the Evaporated: Gone with the Godsshow page on Apple Podcasts to start your free trial or visit GetTheBinge.com to get access wherever you get your podcasts.       A Campside Media &amp; Sony Music Entertainment production. Find more great podcasts from SonyMusic Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Introducing... The Evaporated: Gone with the Gods</title><link>https://open.spotify.com/episode/3MAHamzVTeVzM0mkyuPzmG</link><description>What if someone close to you just … vanished one day? That happens to tens of thousands of families a year in Japan, and it happened to Jake Adelstein, too, back in 2018 — when his accountant disappeared, just before tax day. Adelstein, the author of Tokyo Vice, and co-host Shoko Plambeck go in search of that missing accountant, and take us on a  journey into the fascinating and bizarre world of Japan’s johatsu, or “evaporated” people.    Subscribe now to unlock all shows on The Binge -All Episodes. All at Once... and you’ll be the first to access The Evaporated: Gone with the Gods as soon as it drops on December 12, 2022. A Campside Media &amp; Sony Music Entertainment production. Find out more about The Binge and other podcasts from Sony Music Entertainment at sonymusic.com/podcasts Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>